Do you think they have
yesterday's Daily News?
你想他们有昨天的报纸吗?
I just wanna check my horoscope,
see if it was right.
我只是想看我的星座准不准
Oh, my God! Don't Iook now.
Behind you there's a guy...
天啊,菲比,别看
你背后有个将会令我们
...who can break our hearts
and plunge us into depression.
伤心欲绝的帅哥
Come to mama.
到妈妈这来呀.
He's coming.Be cool.Be cool.
他来了,酷一点…
-Nice hat.-Thanks.
-帽子不错.-谢谢
-We should do something. Whistle.
-I' m not whistling.
-我们应该有所行动,吹口哨
-我不吹
Come on, do it!
来吧,吹!
Do it. Do it. Do it. Do it.
吹.吹.吹.
I can't believe you did that.
我不敢相信你居然这么干了.
The One With Mrs. Bing
-It's all my fault.
-No, it's mine.
-这都是我的错.
-不,是我的错.
Why did I whoo-hoo?
我为什么要"喔-呵"的叫呢?
Was I hoping
he'd turn around and say...
难道我期望,他回过头来然后说……
... " I Iove that sound.
I must have you now"?
……“我喜欢那声音,我现在就要你”?
I wish there was something
we could do.
我只希望我们能帮上一点忙
Hello, coma guy.
你好,昏迷的帅哥
Get up, you Girl Scout!
Up, up, up!
起来,你这少女侦察机!
起来!起来!起来!
What are you doing?
菲此,你在干什么?
Maybe nobody's tried this.
或许没人试过这一招
I wish we at least knew his name.
希望至少能知道他的名字
I hate that they're
calling him John Doe.
我讨厌他们叫他"某约翰"(无名氏)
It's so sad. It's Iike he's a deer,
a female deer.
这真让人伤心.感觉他像一只小鹿
一只小雌鹿
Oh, I was gonna stop.
喔,我就此打住.
Look at that face.
瞧他这张脸
Even sleeping he Iooks smart.
即使他在昏迷中仍一副聪明样
Yeah, but the dents in his knuckles
mean he's artistic.
你有看见他手关节上的凹凸?
那代表他有艺术气息
Okay. He's a lawyer who teaches
sculpting on the side.
他是个兼职教雕塑的律师
And he can dance.
而且他会跳舞
And he's the kind of guy who,
when you're talking, he's Iistening...
他是那种静静听你讲话的人
... not saying, " I understand "...
而不是说”我了解”
... but really wondering
what you look like naked.
却猜想著你裸体的样子
I wish all guys could be Iike him.
我希望男生都像他这样
I know.
我知道
You don't even know this guy.
你们甚至不认识这小伙.
Are there no conscious men
in the city for you two?
纽约难道没有适合你们的清醒男生?
He doesn't have anyone.
他身旁没人照顾
We feel kind of responsible.
我们觉得应该负起责任
I can't believe you said "whoo-hoo. "
我不敢相信你会"喔-呵"
I don't even say "whoo-hoo. "
连我都不说"喔-呵"
Oh, she's coming up.
oh,她出现了
When we return, we 'll talk with
the always interesting Nora Tyler Bing.
稍后,我们将和永远引人人胜的
诺拉.泰勒.宾进行访谈
Put the kids to bed for this one.
你得叫你的孩子上床睡觉了
Don't watch this. Weekend at Bernie 's
is on Showtime and HBO.
我们别看这个
电影台有许多好电影
No way.
不行,这怎么可以
-She's your mom.
-Exactly. Weekend at Bernie's.
-她是你妈妈!
-准确的说是."柏尼斯之周末夜"
Dead guy getting hit
in the groin 20, 30 times.
死人的腹股沟被打二,三十次
I gotta tell you,
I Iove your mom's books.
钱德,我得告诉你
我爱你妈的书
I can't get on a plane without one.
This is so cool.
飞机上没她的书陪伴,我会度日如年
她的书简直是酷毙了
You wouldn't think so
if you were 11...
你无法想象当你11岁的时候
...and your friends were passing around
page 79 of Mistress Bitch.
你的朋友们争相传阅
”情妇婊子”79页时的感觉.
I remember page 79.
我记得第79页.
The thing after the opera
with the girl with the trick hip?
歌剧之后
和那个有可爱臀部的小姑娘的故事
I Iove your mom.I think she's a blast.
拜托,我爱你妈.她是第一流的
That's because she's not your mom.
这是因为她不是你妈妈.
Oh, please. She's the
拜托
Hi, sweetie.
亲爱的
When did "Rigatoni" get back from Rome?
那个"波纹贝壳状通心粉(保罗的头发)"
什么时候从罗马回来的?
-Last night.-Really?
-昨晚.-真的?
So, his plane didn't explode
in a big ball of fire?
难道,他的飞机没在空中炸成火球?
Just a dream I had.
只是我做过的一个梦
But, phew!
Hey, she's on.
她出现了
Nora Bing.
诺拉宾
Back to the book. What is this
about you being arrested in London?
等会儿再谈你的书吧
听说你在伦敦被逮捕?
Your mom was arrested?
你妈被逮捕?
I'm busy beaming with pride.
安静,我正感到无比的骄傲
This is kind of embarrassing...
说来有点难为情...
...but occasionally, after
I've been intimate with a man...
...在我不经意和一个男人亲热后
Why would she say that's embarrassing?
她怎会说难为情?
...I just get this craving
for kung pao chicken.
...我非常想吃宫保鸡丁.
That's too much information.
透露太多了!
Needless to say, he got a huge tip.
不必说,他当然有一个大家伙
Oh, God, I Iove her!
oh,上帝,我爱她!
I think I' m having a stroke.
我想我很有节奏感.
So how is your book tour going?
现在你正为新书做宣传,情况如何?
Oh, fine. I'm leaving
for New York tomorrow, which I hate.
还不错,明天我将前往纽约
其实我不喜欢纽约
But I get to see my son, who I love.
我的儿子住那儿,我爱他.
This is the way that I find out.
Most moms use the phone.
这就是我了解这个的方式.
而大多数母亲只会透过电话这么说.
Don 't take this wrong, I just
don 't see you as a mom.
别会错意,只是我看不出你已为人母
-I don 't mean that bad.
-Oh, no. I'm a fabulous mom.
-我绝对没有恶意
-不,我是个很前卫的母亲
I bought my son his first condoms.
我儿子的第一个保险套,是我买给他的
And then he burst into flames.
然后他就欲火焚身
Let's see. Congress is debating
a new deficit-reduction bill.
国会正讨论新削减预算赤字法案
The mayor wants to raise subway fares.
The high today was 45.
市长想再度提高地铁票价
今天最高气温是45度
And teams played sports.
还有各球队正在比赛
What about GIen?
格伦如何?
He could be a Glen.
可以叫他格伦
Not special enough.
不,还不够特别
How about Agamemnon?
阿伽门农(荷马史诗英雄)怎么样?
Way too special.
太特别了
I'm famished. What do I want?
我饿死了,我想吃什么呢?
Please, God, don't let it be
kung pao chicken.
拜托,别又是宫保鸡丁
You watched the show.
What did you think?
你看了那节目,感觉如何?
I think you need to come out
of your shell.
我觉得你应该更放开一些…
What is this dive?
为何选在这种二流餐厅?
Only you could've picked this place.
只有你才会选这种地方
Come on. Shut up. It's fun.
Give me a hug.
闭嘴,这样满不错的
来,抱一个
I heard about the divorce.
Lesbian, huh?
我听说了离婚的事情了.女同性恋?
Well, you know what they say:
Be careful what you wish for.
你知道他们总是说:“要小心你内心希望的.”
-I think we' re ready for some tequila.
-I know I am.
-我想我们可以喝点龙舌酒了
-我知道我可以
-Who's doing shots?
-Hit me.
-谁要来一杯
-我要
There you go. Ross?
这是你的,罗斯?
I' m not really a shot-drinking
kind of guy.
我不喝酒
Hi. Sorry we' re Iate.
抱歉,我们迟到了
We kind of just, you know,
lost track of time.
我们有点忘了时间
But a man can change.
男人可以改变
Anyone want me to appraise anything?
有人要我评价任何事物吗?
Well, I' m gonna go to tinker-town.
我要去补锅镇
Mrs.Bing, I've read
everything you've written.
宾太太,我拜读过你所有的大作
When I read Euphoria at Midnight,
I wanted to become a writer.
我读”浪漫夜”后,就一心想成为作家
Oh, please.
If I can do it, anybody can.
别这么说,我能办到大家都能办到
Start with half a dozen
European cities...
你只需先描述半打欧洲城市
...throw in 30 euphemisms
for male genitalia...
以委婉语形容男性生殖器
...and you've got yourself a book.
这样就能写成一本书了
My mother, Iadies and gentlemen.
各位,我母亲
Yeah, any messages for room 226?
226房有留言吗?
-You okay, slugger?
-Oh, yeah. I' m fine.
-你还好吧,猛男?
-我还好
What is with you tonight?
你今晚怎么了?
Nothing. Nothing, nothing.
没什么
Okay, thank you.
谢谢
It's the Italian hand-licker, isn't it?
是因为那个意大利舔手男?
No. It's the one he's licking.
不,是因为被他舔的人
She's supposed to be with you.
她应该和你在一起
You' re good.
你真行
I have sold 100 million copies
of my books, and you know why?
罗斯,我卖出上亿本的书
知道为什么吗?
The girl on the cover
with her nipples showing?
因为封面上的辣妹露两点?
No, because I know how to write men
that women fall in Iove with.
不,因为我知道该如何描写让女人陷入爱河的男人
I cannot sell a Paolo.
相信我,保罗没有卖点
People will not turn 325 pages
for a Paolo.
没人有兴趣翻325页看保罗的
Come on.The guy's a secondary character.
他不过是个二等货
He's just a complication
you eventually kill off.
不过是最后被你终结的纠葛
When?
什么时候?
He's not a hero.
他不是主角
You know who our hero is?
知道我们的最佳男主角是谁?
The guy on the cover
with his nipples showing?
露两点的猛男?
No, it's you.
是你啊
-Please.-No, really.
-不要这么说.-不,我是说真的
Come on. You' re smart. You' re sexy.
你既聪明又性感
-Right.-Yes, you are.
-真的.-是呀.
The fact that you don't think you are
makes you sexier.
事实是,你不认为自己比以前更性感了.
Come on, kiddo.
You' re gonna be fine, believe me.
你会走出阴霾的,相信我
I'II just pee in the street.
我到街上尿就好了
Is Chandler here?
钱德在吗
Wait. Come here.
等等.过来.
Okay, about last night...
ok,关于昨天晚上
...you know...
你知道的
... Chandler, you didn't tell....
钱德,你没有告诉他吧
We don't need to tell Chandler.
It was just a kiss. No big deal, right?
因为我想不需告诉他
只是个吻,没什么大不了的
Right. No big deal.
对,没什么大不了的
In bizarro world.
在疯狂世界中才叫没什么
You broke the code.
你违反规定
-What code?
-You don't kiss your friend's mom.
-什么规定?
-不能亲朋友母亲的规定
Sisters are okay.
Maybe a hot-looking aunt.
姐妹还可以
火辣的姑妈,或许也行
But not a mom. Never a mom.
母亲不行,绝对不行
What are you guys doing out here?
你们在外面干什么?
Joey and I had discussed getting
in an early morning racquetball game.
乔和我说过要早起去打回力球
But apparently somebody overslept.
显然有人睡过头
Well, you don't have your racquet.
对,你没带球?
No. No, I don't
because it's being restrung.
不,我的拍子拿去换线了
Somebody was supposed to bring me one.
有人应该帮我准备一支拍子
Well, you didn't call
and leave your grip size.
是吗?你没说握把的尺寸
You guys are spending
way too much time together.
你们俩真会浪费时间
I' m scum. I' m scum.
好吧,我是人渣,我是人渣
-How could you let this happen?
-I don't know.
-罗斯,你怎能让这种事发生?
-我也不知道
It's not Iike she's a regular mom.
她不像是一般的妈妈
She's sexy. She's....
她很性感
You don't think my mom's sexy?
你认为我妈不性感?
Well, not in the same way.
不一样的性感
I'll have you know, Gloria Tribbiani
was a handsome woman in her day.
我妈当年也是美得吓吓叫
You think it's easy giving birth
to seven children?
你认为生7个小孩是件容易的事?
Okay, I think we're getting
into a weird area here.
我们愈谈愈离谱了
What are you doing here?
你们在这儿干什么?
Not playing racquetball.
不是打回力球
-He forgot to Ieave his grip size.
-He didn't get the goggles.
-他忘了告诉我握把尺寸
-他没带护目镜
Sounds like you two have issues.
你们似乎有点争执
Goodbye, baby.
再见,宝贝.
Do they wait for me to do this?
他们在等我做这件事?
-Are you gonna tell him?
-Why would I tell him?
-你到底要不要告诉他?
-为何要告诉他?
If you don't, his mother might.
如果你不说他妈或许会
What are you guys doing here?
你们在这儿干什么?
He's not even wearing a jock strap.
他没穿护裆
What did I ask?
我刚问什么?
What are you doing here?
你在这儿干什么?
Nothing. I just thought
I'd stop by, you know, after...
没事,我只是顺路…
我被那个,你知道的,就是那个
...that I, you know.
那个,我,你知道的.
So, what are you doing here?
你来这儿干什么?
I' m not really here.
我不是专程来此
I just thought I'd drop these off
on the way. My way.
只是顺路拿这些过来
Do you come here a lot...
你常自己来?
...without me?
一个人来?
No, no, no.
没有
Do you think he's doing any better
than he was this morning?
你认为他早上好点没?
How would I know? I wasn't here.
我怎会知道?我又没来
Really? Not even to change his pajamas?
真的?也没替他换睡衣?
Oh, my God.
我的天.
You're my friend.
I had to tell you.
你是我朋友,我得告诉你
I can't believe it.
我简直不敢相信
Paolo kissed my mom?
保罗亲了我妈?
I don't know if you noticed,
but he drank a Iot.
对,我不知道你是否注意到
他喝了很多酒
I mean, you know how he gets
他酒醉的模样你也见识过
I can't do this. I did it.
我办不到…是我
It was me. I' m sorry.
I kissed your mom.
抱歉,是我亲了你妈
What?
什么?
I was upset about Rachel and
I had too much tequila, and Nora...
瑞秋和保罗的事令我很沮丧
我想我是喝太多龙舌酒,诺拉
... Mrs. Mom, your Bing, was...
诺拉,妈妈太太,宾
... being nice.
But nothing happened.
你的宾对我很体贴
但没发生什么事
Nothing. Ask Joey.
什么都没有,可以问乔伊
-Joey came in
-You knew about this?
-乔依刚好走进来
-你知道这件事?
You know, knowledge is a tricky thing.
知识是很狡猾的
Why didn't you tell me?
你为何没告诉我?
You're Iucky I caught them, or else
who knows what would've happened?
他们被我逮到算你幸运
不然后果可不堪设想
Thanks, man. Big help.
谢了,老兄,大忙一个
What the hell were you thinking?
你到底在想什么?
I wasn't. I don't know. I
我没有…我不知道
No one knows the crap I go through
with my mom more than you.
我和我妈之间的鸟事
朋友中属你最清楚了
-I know.
-I can't believe you did this.
-我知道
-我无法相信你会做这种事
-Me neither.
-I' m mad at you too.
-我也无法相信
-我也对你很生气.
-Why are you mad at me?
-Let me slam the door.
-为什么生我的气 ?
-让我用力关门吧
I didn't kiss her. See what happens
when you break the code?
钱德,我没亲她,
违反规定就是这种下场
"A Woman Undone,
by Rachel IKaren Greene. "
”丢脸的女人”瑞秋凯伦格林
I thought I'd give it a shot.
I'm on the first chapter.
对,我想尝试一下,我仍在写第一章
Do you think his "love stick" can be
"liberated from its denim prison"?
你认为他”粗棉布监牢”中的”爱棒”
能获得解放吗?
Yeah, I'd say so.
我想可以吧
And there's no "J " in "engorged. "
我也这么认为,另外你拼错词了
-You going to the hospital tonight?
-No. You?
-你今晚要去医院吗?
-没有,你呢?
No. You?
没有,你呢?
You just asked me.
你刚问过了
Maybe it was a trick question.
好吧,或许这是个圈套
Rachel, can we do this now?
瑞秋,我们现在能开始了吗?
I am so hot.
我好兴奋
Here's my mom and dad
on their wedding day.
这是我爸妈在婚礼时照的
Now, you tell me she's not a knockout.
你告诉我,她不是旷世美人
-I can't believe this conversation.
-Just try to picture her not pregnant.
-没想到我们会谈论这个
-就试着想像她没挺著大肚子
Central Perk is proud to present
Miss Phoebe Buffay.
中央公园很荣幸为各位介绍
菲比鲍费小姐
Thanks.
谢谢
I'd Iike to start with a song
about a man I recently met...
这首歌是有关个我刚认识的男生
...who's come to be
very important to me.
他已成为我生命中重要的男人
You don 't have to be awake
To be my man
你无须醒来当我的男人
Long as you have brain waves
I'll be there to hold your hand
只要你一息尚存
我就会在一旁守候
Though we just met the other day
虽然我们相遇不久
There 's something I have got to say
我想说...
Thank you very much.
I' m gonna take a short break.
谢谢各位,我得休息一下
That was Phoebe Buffay, everybody.
我们感谢菲比小姐.
-What the hell was that?
-Phoebe just started
-她在搞什么东西?
-菲比刚…
I was talking to Joey.
AII right, there, mother-kisser?
我是和乔伊讲话,亲我妈妈的人
" Mother-kisser. "
亲我妈妈的人
I'll shut up.
我闭嘴
I know you' re still mad at me...
我知道你仍在生我的气
... but there were two people
there that night.
我只想说那一夜有两个人
-There were two sets of lips.
-I expect this from her.
-两双嘴唇
-是哦,我希望她亲口告诉我
She's always been a Freudian nightmare.
她一直都是个佛洛依德梦魇
Then why don't you say something?
你为何不找她谈谈?
Because it's complicated.
It's complex.
因为太复杂了,这是个情结
You kissed my mom.
你亲了我妈
We' re rehearsing a Greek play.
我们正在排练希腊剧
That's funny.
Are we done now?
真幽默,排练完没?
You mean you' re not gonna
tell her how you feel?
还没,你不找她谈?
不说出你的感受?
Just because you played
tonsil tennis with my mom...
别因为你亲过她
...doesn't mean you know her.
You can't talk to her.
就自以为了解她
相信我,不能找她谈
Okay. "You can't"?
Or you can't?
到底是能还是不能?
Okay, that's my finger.
我的手指
Okay, that's my knee.
我的膝盖
Still doing the play.
还在排练
What did you do with him?
你对他怎么了?
-You're awake.-Look at you.
-你醒了.-你瞧你,
How do you feel?
感觉如何?
A little woozy, but basically okay.
头有点晕,基本上还行
Gosh, you Iook good.
你的气色好极了
I feel good.
我感觉好极了
Who are you?
你们是谁?
-Sorry.-I'm Phoebe.
-对不起.-我叫菲比
I' m Monica.
I've been caring for you.
我叫摩妮卡
我一直在照顾你
We both have.
我们一直在照顾你
-The Etch A Sketch is from you?
-Actually, me.
-蚀刻艺术是你们送的?
-其实只有我一个
-I got you the foot massager.
-I shaved you.
-我替你做脚底按摩
-知道是谁帮你刮胡子的吗?是我
-I read to you.
-I sang.
-我念书给你听
-我唱歌给你听
Well, thanks.
谢了
-Oh, my pleasure.
-You' re welcome.
-我的荣幸
-没关系.
So I guess I'II see you around.
我想那就再见了
What? That's it?
什么?就这样?
"See you around "?
再见?
-What do you want me to say?
-I don't know.
-不然要我说什么?
-我不知道
Maybe...
或许
... "That was nice. "
该说你们真好
" It meant something to me. "
向我表白吧
" I'II call you. "
我会打电话给你们的
-Okay. I'II call you.
-I don't think you mean that.
-好吧,我会打的
-一点诚意都没有
This is so typical.
男生都这样
You know, we give and we give...
我们付出,付出
...and we give.
不断的付出
And we just get nothing back.
却得到任何回报
And then one day, you wake up,
and it's, "See you around. "
有一天他醒来却只说再见
Let's go, Phoebe.
走吧菲比
You know what?
We thought you were different.
知道吗?我们以为你与众不同
But I guess it was just the coma.
我想这只是昏迷的缘故
The car's waiting. I just wanted
to drop off my book for your friends.
楼下的车已发动
我只想拿几本我的书给你朋友
Autographed.
And give you a goodbye kiss.
有我的亲笔签名.来一个吻别.
Here's the kiss,
here's the goodbye....
这是一个吻
这是告别……
-Anything you want from Lisbon?
-Just knowing you're there is enough.
-需要我在里斯本帮你买什么吗?
-不需要,知道你要去就够了
AII right. Well, be good.
I Iove you.
好吧,要乖哦,我爱你
You kissed my best Ross.
你亲了我最好的罗斯
Or something to that effect.
好像说错了,反正差不多
Look, it was stupid.
好吧,我做了蠢事
-Really stupid.
-愚蠢至极
I don't even know how it happened.
我也不知道是怎么发生的
I' m sorry, honey. I promise
it will never happen again.
抱歉,孩子,我保证不会再发生这种事
Really, really stupid.
真的愚蠢至极
真的,真的愚蠢之极
-Are we okay now?-Yeah.
-你感觉好点吗?>-是的
No.
不
The forbidden love
of a man and his door.
男人与门之间禁忌的爱
He told her off. And not just
about the kiss.
他说了,不只是亲吻的事
一切都说出来了
You're kidding?
你在开玩笑?
He said, "When are you gonna
start being a mom? "
他说你何时才能成熟
开始当个妈?
Then she said:
等等,她回答说
"The question is, when are you gonna
realize I have a bomb? "
你何时才能长大了解
我是个性感女郎?
Are you sure she didn't say:
等等,你确定她不是说
"When are you gonna grow up
and realize I am your mom? "
你何时才能长大了解
我是你妈?
-That makes more sense.
-You think?
-这样比较合理
-你也这样认为?
What's going on now?
现在情况怎么样?
I don't know. I've been standing here
spelling it out for you.
我不知道.我一直在这儿说给你听
I don't hear anything. Wait.
我什么都听不到,等等…
What do you see?
你看见什么?
It's hard to tell.
They're tiny and upside down.
很难说,他们好小而且上下颠倒
Wait, wait, wait.
等等，等等
They're walking away.
他们走过来,他们走过去
No, they' re not. They' re coming
right at us. Run!
不,不是.他们走过来了,快逃
-Are you okay, kiddo?
-Yeah, I' m okay.
-你还好吧,孩子?
-还好
All right. You be good.
希望都好
Drive safe.
小心开车.
-Mrs. Bing.
-Mr. Geller.
-你好,宾太太
-你好,盖勒.
You mean that?
你当真?
Yeah, why not?
对,有何不可?
So I told her.
我告诉她了
-How did it go?
-Awful. Awful.
-情况怎么样?
-简直是可笑到了极点
Couldn't have gone worse.
没有比这更糟糕的啦.
-Well, how do you feel?
-Pretty good.
-感觉怎样
-不错
I told her.
我告诉她了
Well, see?
瞧,看到没有?
So maybe it wasn't such a bad idea,
me kissing your mom, huh?
或许我亲你妈不是个馊主意…
But we don't have to
go down that road.
我们不必继续往下说了吧
This is just the first chapter...
这只是第一章
...and I want your absolute
honest opinion. Okay?
我要大家坦白的意见
And on page two, he's not reaching
for her " heaving beasts. "
在第二页中
他的手没伸向她那灰尖挺的双峰
She could have heaving beasts.
她本来可以有尖挺的双峰
Right, but in this case she doesn't.
好吧,在这里她没有.
What's a " niffle"?
什么是”如头”?
You can usually find them
on the heaving beasts.
通常在双峰上可以找到
Okay, so I' m not a great typist.
好吧…算我不会打字
Did you get to the part
about his "huge, throbbing pens"?
看到这里没有"他那巨大,颤动的笔"
You don't wanna be around
when he starts writing with those.
他用那支笔时你不会想在场的
That's it. Give them back.
够了,还我…
Wait, I just got to the part
about her "public hair. "
等等,我才刚刚看到她的"公共头发".